# **Gyuhyeon Hwang**

## Junior backend developer

4th-grade student backend developer specializing in Python/Django development. Familiar with collaboration through the internship and team project experience with Git and Notion. Use Python and C++ as my primary language and usually participated in data analysis and web development.

## **Contact**

#### **Email:**

hwgyuhyeon@gmail.com

#### Portfolio:

hgyuhyeon.github.io

## **Education**

## Department of Computer Science – Chungbuk National University

Bachelor of Science 2019.03 – Now

# Computer Science – Angelo State University

Study Abroad 2022.01 – 2022.05

## Languages

English – B2

Korean - Native

Japanese – A2

## Skill

- Python, C++
- MySQL, SQLite
- Git, Notion

- Django, DRF
- RESTful API

## **Experience**

### **Backend Developer**, 2022.06 – 2022.07

Silicon-Valley internship program, Remote

- Experience with all stages of the development cycle.
- Design structure of the Django backend server and develop GET playlists and GET one playlist API.
- Apply the AI model and React frontend project to the Django backend server.
- Connect Django, MySQL, Nginx, and React via docker-compose and deploy to AWS EC2.

## Web Developer, 2021.06 - 2021.07

Flug Mediaworks, Cheongju, South Korea

- Implement a web page including PHP/JavaScript backend and HTML/CSS frontend based on a designed draft.
- Translate the Korean website to English and apply it to the English version with a session.

## **Project**

#### **Backend Developer**, 2021.05 – 2021.12

Lunar AI, Chungbuk national university AI club COSMIC

- Al-based intelligent surveillance system.
- Develop POST face detection API and GET detection result API.
- Design and manage all data including face detection and user with MySQL.